Dnyaneshwar ShekadeSystem Engineer



Education

MASTERS IN SCIENCE: COMPUTER SCIENCE-2023

8.1 GRADE
DEPARTMENT OF COMPUTER SCINECE
UNIVERSITY OF MUMBAI, VIDHYANAGRI
SANTACUZ

BACHELOR OF SCIENGE: COMPUTER SCIENCE - 2021

6.5 GRADE

N.G ACHARYA AND D.K MARATHE COLLEGE, UNIVERSITY OF MUMBAI, CHEMBUR

Certifications

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATION AND IT INFRASTRUCTURE SERVICES -GOOGLE

INTRODUCTION TO MICROSOFT AZURE CLOUD SERVICES – MICROSOFT

Skills

- System Administration, Linux, Windows
- Networking
- Server Virtualization
- System Desktop troubleshooting
- Software installation and troubleshooting
- Data migration
- IT infrastructure implementation.

NAS virtualization, Firewall, routers

+91 7039997894 shekade31@gmail.com linkedIn.com/dnyanesh1

Summary

Experienced Computer System Engineer proficient in enhancing operational efficiency and profitability through comprehensive analysis and technical expertise. Successful in providing strategic guidance to large corporations, small businesses, and individual clients. Specialties include system design, implementation, and risk mitigation.

Experience

SYSTEM ENGINEER - 01/2023 to PRESENT RELIANCE INDUSTRIES LIMITED/GEEKAY INFOTECH, RCP GHANSOLI

- Handling Desktop related issue via remote access.
- Installation of whitelist application in reliance network.
- Giving access to particular website from active directory.
- Data Loss Prevention issue handling.
- Working on Windows patches.
- Office 365 and office 2019 issue handle also migrate users for azure license
- Testing Accops and Citrix desktop for virtualization
- Testing and Implement Linux ubuntu In Reliance network.

HARDWARE ENGINEER - 03/2022 to 09/2022 VIVACONNECT PVT LTD, ANDHERI

- Handling network related issues on systems.
- Implement Linux mint in Vivaconnect.
- Create proxmos severs for work from home users.
- Handling VPN Access and rules in firewall
- Windows OS hardening as per company policy.
- Assert management and implement ticketing tool.
- Dealing with vendors for hardware's and warranty related issues.
- Antivirus and DLP monitoring.
- Linux installation and windows installation

HARDWARE ENGINEER - 01/2021 to 02/2022 **LAPTOP BUCKET SHOP**, Vashi

- Software installation and hardware installation
- Troubleshoot hardware related issues in desktop